Guide to the Pettigrew Papers
Yale University Library
- Additional Correspondence, 1803-1865; Series II.; 2.5' (9 boxes)
  - Jackson, W., 1859 (Box 17, Folder 846)
  - James, [I.], n.d. (Box 17, Folder 847)
  - Jehring, E., 1834 (Box 17, Folder 848)
    1 ALS to T.J. Pettigrew. 1 calling card.
  - Jenkins, Rev. Henry, 1859-60 (Box 17, Folder 849)
  - Jervis, Swynfen, 1861 (Box 17, Folder 850)
  - Jessop, C. Moore, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 851)
  - Jessop, Thomas, [1859 or later] (Box 17, Folder 852)
  - Johnson, Henry James, [1837 or later] (Box 17, Folder 853)
  - Johnson, James, 1829-1850 (Box 17, Folder 854)
  - [Jollins], Thomas, [1839 or later] (Box 17, Folder 855)
  - Jones, H. [Bruce], [1860 or later] (Box 17, Folder 856)
  - Jones, Michael, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 857)
  - Jones, Willoughby, 1857 (Box 17, Folder 858)
  - Jordan, Mr., [1828 or later] (Box 17, Folder 859)
  - Keane, [Dan], [1831] (Box 17, Folder 860)
  - Keate, Col., [1829 or later] (Box 17, Folder 861)
  - Kenrick, John, 1850 (Box 17, Folder 862)
  - Keppel, Edward J., [1824] (Box 17, Folder 863)
  - [Kempleheader, J.], 1843-47 (Box 17, Folder 864)
  - Kirkmann, [Abraham], 1846 (Box 17, Folder 865)
  - Klein, C., 1851 (Box 17, Folder 866)
    LS to "the honourable President and the Secretaries of the Archaiologic Society in London"
  - Labram, Frederick, 1860 (Box 18, Folder 867)
    ALS to R. Smith. Attached sketch of an artifact.
  - Laher, J., 1858 (Box 18, Folder 868)
    ALS to Mme. [deBuy]
  - Lancaster, Henry, 1852 (Box 18, Folder 869)
  - Langshaw, J.P., 1850 (Box 18, Folder 870)
  - Laton, Prof., 1838 (Box 18, Folder 871)
  - Laurie, Mr., 1824 (Box 18, Folder 872)
  - Lawrance, E., 1850 (Box 18, Folder 873)
  - Le [Harivel], Mr., 1833 (Box 18, Folder 874)
    AL in French to T.J. Pettigrew.
  - [Lee, Mark], 1850 (Box 18, Folder 875)
  - Lehzen, Baroness [Louise], 1838 (Box 18, Folder 876)
  - Levesque, Peter, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 877)
  - Lewis, [H.D.], 1820 (Box 18, Folder 878)
    with a riddle attributed to Dr. Parr
  - Lincoln, S., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 879)
  - Linden, J.T., 1817 (Box 18, Folder 880)
  - Lindsay, John, 1831-52 (Box 18, Folder 881)
    7 ALS to T.J. Pettigrew. One letter contains a plate of Greek numismatic illustrations.
  - Liston, D., 1845 (Box 18, Folder 882)
  - Liston, J., 1839 (Box 18, Folder 883)
  - Lloyd, Mary Ann, 1830 (Box 18, Folder 884)
    ALS to T.J. Pettigrew and AL to the Duke of Sussex.
  - Lodge, J., 1837 (Box 18, Folder 885)
    1 ALS and 1 calling card.
  - Lombe, Edward, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 886)
  - Long, Mr., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 887)
  - Lowe, F. Pindar (Box 18, Folder 888)
  - Lucas, P.B., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 889)
  - Luen, M.P., 1828 (Box 18, Folder 890)
  - Lukis, Frederick, C., [1850] (Box 18, Folder 891)
  - Lupton, Harry, 1852-29 (Box 18, Folder 892)
    3 ALS to Pettigrew. Includes a short verse by Lupton and reference to a publication by Lupton on the accounts of the Church of Thame (1852).
  - Lynn, E., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 893)
  - MacArthur, C., [1816 or later] (Box 18, Folder 894)
  - Macdonnell, P., 1840-42 (Box 18, Folder 895)
  - MacFarlane, Charles, 1832 (Box 18, Folder 896)
  - Macintyre, James, 1858 (Box 18, Folder 897)
  - Mackreth, Thomas, 1850 (Box 18, Folder 898)
  - Madden, Mr. [T.], n.d. (Box 18, Folder 899)
  - Madox, M., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 900)
  - [Maguire], William, [1824-34] (Box 18, Folder 901)
  - Mallock, D., 1832 (Box 18, Folder 902)
  - Maltby, D., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 903)
  - Manchester, J.P., 1850 (Box 18, Folder 904)
  - Maniakes, Mr., [1823 or later] (Box 18, Folder 905)
  - Manners Sutton, J.H., 1852 (Box 18, Folder 906)
  - Mantellin, Mon., 1851 (Box 18, Folder 907)
    ALS in French from the Société Archéologique de l'Orléanais, signed by Mantellin, to the Preseident of the British Archaeological Assoc.
  - Maometto, Sig., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 908)
    ALS in Italian to [T.J. Pettigrew] seeking medical attention.
  - Marable, [Thomas], n.d. (Box 18, Folder 909)
  - Marshall, Chap[lain], 1841 (Box 18, Folder 910)
  - Martin, Mr., 1832 (Box 18, Folder 911)
  - Martin, Viva J., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 912)
  - Mason, J.M., 1817 (Box 18, Folder 913)
  - Matthews, [William], 1803 (Box 18, Folder 914)
    ALS to unknown 3rd party, recommending Vira Fowler as an instructor of children.
  - Maule, William, 1836 (Box 18, Folder 915)
  - Mendham, Mr., 1827 (Box 18, Folder 916)
  - Mentern, B., [1835 or later] (Box 18, Folder 917)
  - Meredith, William, George, [1825 or later] (Box 18, Folder 918)
  - Merle, W[illiam] H[enry], 1832-41 (Box 18, Folder 919)
  - Meyrick, W[illiam], 1853 (Box 18, Folder 920)
  - Mill, R., 1856 (Box 18, Folder 921)
  - Miller, [J.], 1828 (Box 18, Folder 922)
  - Mills, Mr., 1831 (Box 18, Folder 923)
  - Milward, Richard, 1852 (Box 18, Folder 924)
  - Minasi, J., 1849 (Box 18, Folder 925)
    2 AL to Pettigrew. Envelope and calling card. Sonnet in Italian in tribute of Robert Vernon.
  - Moor, Maj., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 926)
    AL to Mr. Hunker
  - Moore, [Mr.], 1845 (Box 18, Folder 927)
  - Moore, Christopher, 1830-49 (Box 18, Folder 928)
  - Moore, J.S., 1851 (Box 18, Folder 929)
  - Moore, Thomas, 1836 (Box 18, Folder 930)
  - Moran, Edward, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 931)
  - Morgan, James, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 932)
    ALS fragment, unknown recipient.
  - Mortimer, J.L., 1842 (Box 18, Folder 933)
  - Mosley, Oswald, [1851] (Box 18, Folder 934)
  - Mühlenfels, Dr. [O. von], 1830 (Box 18, Folder 935)
  - Mullins, Edward, 1846 (Box 18, Folder 936)
  - Mulock, Thomas, 1842 (Box 18, Folder 937)
    ALS to [T.J. Pettigrew] with printed announcement of lecture series by Mulock and James Sheridan Knowles, on literary topics.
  - Mundell, Alexander, 1828-33 (Box 18, Folder 938)
  - Murden, Benjamin, 1850 (Box 18, Folder 939)
  - Murray, Charles A., [1827 or later] (Box 18, Folder 940)
  - Murray, Peter, 1845-52 (Box 18, Folder 941)
  - Murray, T.B., [1831] (Box 18, Folder 942)
  - Myers, Francis Waske H., 1836-44 (Box 18, Folder 943)
  - Neal, John, [1824]-25 (Box 18, Folder 944)
  - Neeld, Mr., 1833 (Box 18, Folder 945)
  - [Neildman, Mr.], 1838-52 (Box 18, Folder 946)
  - Newman, A., 1834 (Box 18, Folder 947)
  - Nicholl, G., 1846 (Box 18, Folder 948)
  - Nicholson, [H.] James, 1852 (Box 18, Folder 949)
  - [Niger], 1851 (Box 18, Folder 950)
  - Nochden, G.H., 1824-25 (Box 18, Folder 951)
- Additional Correspondence, 1857; Series II.
  - Norwich, John, 1857 (Box 18, Folder 952)
  - Nugent, Mr., 1848 (Box 18, Folder 953)
  - O'Brien, A. Stafford, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 954)
  - O'Connor, Arthur, 1852 (Box 18, Folder 955)
  - Ogg, S.W., 1825 (Box 18, Folder 956)
  - Ogilby, D[avid], 1824 (Box 18, Folder 957)
  - Oliveira, B[enjamin], 1836-52 (Box 18, Folder 958)
    2 ALS to T.J. Pettigrew. 1 ALS to Dr. Sigmond
  - Omeara, Mr., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 959)
    1 AL to T.J. Pettigrew. 1 Calling Card.
  - Osborn, Mr., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 960)
  - Osborn, Sir John, 1823 (Box 18, Folder 961)
  - Osborne, Jonathan, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 962)
  - Oylander, Richard, 1855 (Box 18, Folder 963)
  - Palmer, Mr., [1816] (Box 19, Folder 964)
  - Parker, J[on], 1819 (Box 19, Folder 965)
  - Patten, William, 1850 (Box 19, Folder 966)
  - Peel, Edmund (Box 19, Folder 967)
  - Peel, William, 1835 (Box 19, Folder 968)
  - Pembroke, Lady, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 969)
  - [Pener, P.], 1834 (Box 19, Folder 970)
  - Penleaze, John [S], [1832 or later] (Box 19, Folder 971)
  - Penny, Charles, 1850 (Box 19, Folder 972)
  - [Perassh], G., 1848 (Box 19, Folder 973)
  - Perceval, Capt., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 974)
  - Perceval, Frederick, [1843] (Box 19, Folder 975)
  - [Peru], Sir John, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 976)
    AL to Sir J.G. Wilkinson.
  - Petit, Louis Hayes, 1834 (Box 19, Folder 977)
  - Philipper, Mr., 1849 (Box 19, Folder 978)
  - Philips, Mark, 1850 (Box 19, Folder 979)
    2 ALS to T.J. Pettigrew. 1 ALS to W.H. Ainsworth.
  - Phillips, Samuel, 1847 (Box 19, Folder 980)
    1 ALS to T.J. Pettigrew. 1 ALS to [Wright].
  - Pireto, S., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 981)
  - Pole, [C.W.], n.d. (Box 19, Folder 982)
  - Ponton, Thomas, 1835-37 (Box 19, Folder 983)
  - Potter, John, 1850 (Box 19, Folder 984)
  - Pozzo, Count Ferdinand dal, 1837 (Box 19, Folder 985)
    3 ALS and 1 AL to T. J. Pettigrew. 1 ALS from Mme. Mary dal Pozzo to Mrs. Pettigrew.
  - Praetorius, Dr., 1842 (Box 19, Folder 986)
  - Pretty, E., 1850-52 (Box 19, Folder 987)
  - Prior, James, 1832-48 (Box 19, Folder 988)
  - Prosloftsky, P., 1834 (Box 19, Folder 989)
  - Prower, [J.M.], 1847 (Box 19, Folder 990)
  - Purnell, Purnell B., 1849 (Box 19, Folder 991)
  - Radclyffe, William, 1825 (Box 19, Folder 992)
  - Ralioth, M., 1856 (Box 19, Folder 993)
  - Ramsbottom, Mr. [John], [1832 or later] (Box 19, Folder 994)
  - Raymond, George (Box 19, Folder 995)
  - [Rees, Charles G.], 1825 (Box 19, Folder 996)
  - Renuie, George, 1833-35 (Box 19, Folder 997)
    2 ALS. Voucher in name of Mr. and Mrs. Renuie for "Royal Colosseum Fête, Wednesday, July 8, 1835." and printed notice of same event, with writing on back [in Renuie's hand?].
  - Reuvens, C.J.C., 1835 (Box 19, Folder 998)
  - Reynolds, J.H., 1846 (Box 19, Folder 999)
    ALS to Arden.
  - Richardson, Dr. R., 1825-41 (Box 19, Folder 1000)
  - Ridley, [Sir Matthew], 1817 (Box 19, Folder 1001)
    AL to Philosophical Society
  - Ring, Charles S., 1846-47 (Box 19, Folder 1002)
  - Rippen, [E.], [1833 or later] (Box 19, Folder 1003)
  - Rochfort, Maj. Richard, 1817 (Box 19, Folder 1004)
  - Rolfe, W.H., 1845-51 (Box 19, Folder 1005)
  - Roscoe, Dr. [Rd], 1832-38 (Box 19, Folder 1006)
  - Ross, John, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1007)
  - Rouse, John, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1008)
  - Rousedragon, Thomas William King, 1844 (Box 19, Folder 1009)
  - Rouw, Mr. [Peter], [1830]-33 (Box 19, Folder 1010)
  - Rowbotham, Mr., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1011)
  - Rudge, James, 1827-48 (Box 19, Folder 1012)
  - Rue, Dr., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1013)
  - [Rufter], William, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1014)
    ALS to [William Pettigrew?]
  - [Rumny], H.W., 1851 (Box 19, Folder 1015)
  - Sainsbury, J[ohn], 1841 (Box 19, Folder 1016)
    ALS to unidentified third party.
  - Sanford, Edward Ayshford, [1832]-50 (Box 19, Folder 1017)
  - [Sewik, S.C.], [1844 or later] (Box 19, Folder 1018)
  - Seymour, C.F., 1852 (Box 19, Folder 1019)
  - Sharpe, Lancelot, 1836-43 (Box 19, Folder 1020)
  - Shearman, William, 1817-1826 (Box 19, Folder 1021)
  - Sheppard, William, 1841 (Box 19, Folder 1022)
  - Sheridan, Louisa Henrietta, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1023)
  - Sherwill, Markham, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1024)
  - Shippard, W.H., 1845 (Box 19, Folder 1025)
  - Shipsey, Richard, 1843 (Box 19, Folder 1026)
  - Shupson, Samuel, 1850 (Box 19, Folder 1027)
  - Sigmond, G.G., 1827-34 (Box 19, Folder 1028)
  - Silerweve, Egerton, 1850 (Box 19, Folder 1029)
  - Sinclair, Mr., [1839 or later] (Box 19, Folder 1030)
  - Skelton, J., 1832 (Box 19, Folder 1031)
    ALS and ALS fragment.
  - [Slade, Mr.], 1852 (Box 19, Folder 1032)
  - Smirnove, James, 1827-29 (Box 19, Folder 1033)
  - Smirnove, John, 1827 (Box 19, Folder 1034)
  - Smith, Mr. [V.J.], [1835] (Box 19, Folder 1035)
  - Smith, Augustus F., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1036)
  - Smith, Georgina, L., [1833 or later] (Box 19, Folder 1037)
    2 ALS to T.J. Pettigrew. One ALS refers to an enclosure (not included) to be forwarded to her brother Sydney presumably bearing news of a death in the family. Three poems: "We part to meet again", "There are hearts that love once and for ever!", and "Fare thee well!" arranged for guitar and piano, written in Smith's hand.
  - Smith, John, 1828 (Box 19, Folder 1038)
    ALS to the Duke of Sussex. Smith identifies himself as an editor of the "Liverpool Mercury"
  - Smith, John, 1846 (Box 19, Folder 1039)
    70 St. Vincent St. Glasgow. [John Smith operated a book store from this address after 1834].
  - Smith, Leicester, 1849 (Box 19, Folder 1040)
  - Snow, Robert, 1848-50 (Box 19, Folder 1041)
  - Soane, George, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1042)
  - Squibb, G[eorge] J., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1043)
  - Stanfield, J., n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1044)
  - Stanford, John Frederick, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1045)
  - Stanley, J.F., 1831 (Box 19, Folder 1046)
    ALS to T.J. Pettigrew. Stanley signs "Hon. Sec. Pro. Tem."
  - Stanway, G., 1849 (Box 19, Folder 1047)
  - Stephens, [Archibald John], 1846 (Box 19, Folder 1048)
  - Stephens, Henry [J], 1850 (Box 19, Folder 1049)
  - Stidolph, H., 1839 (Box 19, Folder 1050)
    ALS to T.J. Pettigrew. Contains a poem, "To my Dear Maria," dated 1830.
  - Stokac, John, [1827 or later] (Box 19, Folder 1051)
  - Stokes, Jonathan, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1052)
  - Stone, T.A., 1824-38 (Box 19, Folder 1053)
  - Storer, H., 1830 (Box 19, Folder 1054)
  - Swan, J., [1834 or later] (Box 19, Folder 1055)
  - Swinburne, J.E., 1849 (Box 19, Folder 1056)
  - Sylvester, [Lord?], 1852 (Box 19, Folder 1057)
  - Synes, Sarah Bowles, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1058)
  - Taisney, [A.M.], n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1059)
  - Talbot, M. D'arcy, [1829]-33 (Box 20, Folder 1060)
  - Talbot, John H., 1835 (Box 20, Folder 1061)
  - Taylor, [J.W.], n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1062)
  - Tennyson, C[harles], 1827 (Box 20, Folder 1063)
  - Thomas, J.P., 1826-27 (Box 20, Folder 1064)
  - Thomas, Jane [Mrs. Edward], 1849 (Box 20, Folder 1065)
  - Thomas, ----, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1066)
  - Thompson, William, 1838 (Box 20, Folder 1067)
  - Thoms, [Peter P.], 1829-30 (Box 20, Folder 1068)
  - Tibbs, Henry W., 1852 (Box 20, Folder 1069)
  - Tierney, Miss, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1070)
  - Todd, [James] Ruddell, 1833 (Box 20, Folder 1071)
  - Toone, William, 1831 (Box 20, Folder 1072)
  - Torre, Nicholas L., 1835-40 (Box 20, Folder 1073)
  - Tousley, [Mr.], n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1074)
  - Townley, Charles, 1850 (Box 20, Folder 1075)
  - Tucker, Charles, [1825-26] (Box 20, Folder 1076)
  - Turner, Joseph, 1850 (Box 20, Folder 1077)
  - Twining, George, 1842-50 (Box 20, Folder 1078)
  - Twopenny, William, 1843 (Box 20, Folder 1079)
  - Twycross, J., 1842-43 (Box 20, Folder 1080)
    13 ALS to T.J. Pettigrew
  - Tyndale, George Booth, 1827 (Box 20, Folder 1081)
  - Tynte, C.K.K., 1842 (Box 20, Folder 1082)
  - [Tzneh, T.], n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1083)
  - Ure, Alexander, 1843 (Box 20, Folder 1084)
  - Vance, George, 1825-[32] (Box 20, Folder 1085)
  - Veitch, James, 1833-36 (Box 20, Folder 1086)
  - Vernon, G.E.H., 1853 (Box 20, Folder 1087)
  - Wade, Dr. [A.S.], 1826-36 (Box 20, Folder 1088)
  - Walker, Edward, [1850] (Box 20, Folder 1089)
  - Walker, J., 1816-34 (Box 20, Folder 1090)
  - Walker, J.A., 1851 (Box 20, Folder 1091)
  - Walker, P[atrick], [1827 or later] (Box 20, Folder 1092)
  - Wall, Thomas C., 1845 (Box 20, Folder 1093)
  - Waller, John G., [1847 or later] (Box 20, Folder 1094)
  - Walue, Alfred, 1835 (Box 20, Folder 1095)
    ALS to [T.J. Pettigrew], and AL to Mrs. Pettigrew.
  - Warburton, John, [1832 or later] (Box 20, Folder 1096)
  - Ward, J.G., 1852 (Box 20, Folder 1097)
    A note [in Pettigrew's hand?] reads "Dean of Lincoln."
  - Ward, William B., 1830 (Box 20, Folder 1098)
  - Ware, Martin, 1820-45 (Box 20, Folder 1099)
  - Warneford, H.E. Wetherell, 1848 (Box 20, Folder 1100)
  - Warner, D.H. Lee, 1857 (Box 20, Folder 1101)
  - Warner, James Lee, 1857 (Box 20, Folder 1102)
    2 ALS. Refers to D.H. Lee Warner as his uncle (see previous).
  - Warton, Joseph Pitt, 1834 (Box 20, Folder 1103)
    ALS to T.J. Pettigrew and calling card.
  - Waterfield, Dr., [1826 or later] (Box 20, Folder 1104)
  - Waters, Mr., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1105)
  - Watts, Robert, 1827 (Box 20, Folder 1106)
  - Webb, William, 1846-47 (Box 20, Folder 1107)
  - Webster, Dr., 1830 (Box 20, Folder 1108)
  - Welsh, J.J., 1829 (Box 20, Folder 1109)
  - Welsh, James, [1828] (Box 20, Folder 1110)
  - Wheatley, [Sir Henry], 1835 (Box 20, Folder 1111)
    ALS to G.G. Sigmond and T.J. Pettigrew.
  - Wheatstone, C., 1836 (Box 20, Folder 1112)
  - Whiston, C., 1844 (Box 20, Folder 1113)
  - Whitaker, T.H., 1850 (Box 20, Folder 1114)
  - White, John, 1853 (Box 20, Folder 1115)
  - White, W., 1816 (Box 20, Folder 1116)
  - Whiting, John, 1842 (Box 20, Folder 1117)
  - Whitmore, Mr., 1829 (Box 20, Folder 1118)
  - Whitwell, C.V., [1814-16] (Box 20, Folder 1119)
    2 ALS to the Rev. Maurice.
  - Wickes, C., [1851] (Box 20, Folder 1120)
  - Widdowron, Jo., 1830 (Box 20, Folder 1121)
  - Wight, John, 1827-30 (Box 20, Folder 1122)
  - Wilcox, Richard, 1846 (Box 20, Folder 1123)
  - Wilkin, J.W., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1124)
  - Wilks, G.A., 1838 (Box 20, Folder 1125)
  - Williams, Dr., [1826 or later] (Box 20, Folder 1126)
  - Williams, Mr., [1857 or later] (Box 20, Folder 1127)
  - Williams, Joseph L., 1845-46 (Box 20, Folder 1128)
  - Williamson, B., 1836 (Box 20, Folder 1129)
  - Wallich, Charles M., 1840-43 (Box 20, Folder 1130)
  - Windsor, Mrs. [Thomas], 1829 (Box 20, Folder 1131)
  - Wood, [Benjamin], [1831 or later] (Box 20, Folder 1132)
  - Woodin, [J.S.], 1831 (Box 20, Folder 1133)
  - Woods, Albert W., 1842-48 (Box 20, Folder 1134)
  - Woods, William, 1830-37 (Box 20, Folder 1135)
  - Woodward, Charles, 1841 (Box 20, Folder 1136)
  - Wooler, Thomas James, [1832] (Box 20, Folder 1137)
    ALS to Mr. [Yorston]
  - Woolrych, H. Fitzroy, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1138)
  - Word, Col., 1827 (Box 20, Folder 1139)
  - Worsaae, [Jens Jacob Amussen], 1847 (Box 20, Folder 1140)
  - Worthington, W.H., 1829 (Box 20, Folder 1141)
  - Wright, James, 1845 (Box 20, Folder 1142)
  - Wright, Lemuel W., 1830-31 (Box 20, Folder 1143)
  - Wright, Mary Atkyns, 1829 (Box 20, Folder 1144)
  - Wyon, B., 1847 (Box 20, Folder 1145)
  - Yates, W. Holt, 1844 (Box 20, Folder 1146)
  - Yend, [M], 1849 (Box 20, Folder 1147)
  - [Youlang, William], n.d. (Box 20, Folder 1148)
    ALS to Dr. [William?] Meyrick with pencil note: "for T. Pettigrew Esq."
  - Unidentified and incomplete (Box 21, Folder 1149-1150)
    34 ALS, 3 AL, 9 incomplete ALS, MS poetry fragment, Medical log (in French). Various recipients.
  - Calling cards, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1151)
    Dr. Ameline; Dr. David Badham; Sir Charles Bagot; Lord [Belliarch]; Ch[evalier] Dupin; Dr. Fellowes; Miss Hamlet [with note on back from W. Maginn]; Vice Admiral Sir Edward King; A. Marco; M. Orlando; Mr. Roscoe.
  - Cover sheets, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1152)
  - Empty envelopes, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1153)
  - Miscellaneous fragments, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1154)
  - Photographic material, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 1155)
    Subject: [T.J. Pettigrew], unknown format; note on reverse.
  - Printed material (Box 21, Folder 1156)
    - Title page of Esquisse D'une Histoire de la Médecine et de la Chirurgie [by Koraes, Adamantios, 1748-1833], signed [W.G.] Blair., n.d.
    - [Obituary of Elizabeth Heberden, d. 1754]
      Multiple copies, with cover sheet addressed to T.J. Pettigrew [cover sheet date 1836 or later]
    - Prospectus for restoration of tomb and monument of Shakespeare and establishment of a museum and library of his works
    - Descriptions (in French) of various temples and deities, "Bengale, Bénarès. 1829, L.P."
    - Notice of sale of books about art and antiquities by Guillame Zahn, Signed by Zahn on reverse
    - One page from an English Bible
      - [f. 117, Revelation of St. John, ch. 12-14], [n.d.]